[{"answer": " I wish I could get excited. Really. That's the truth. As excited as you, over such... simple things", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You are", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I lost three me.  You killed them, my friend. You did... and I did. Because I didn't know what to expect... because you... didn't tell me", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Anything! I wasn't told anything", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " How ya doin' , my friend? Good to see ya. Glad you're still alive. Same here, colonel, I'm..", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " The same way those fuckin' dogs got out! Through their pens!  I... locked them off", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Not simple", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " I forgot. You're never confused. So...what's right, Mohawk? And what's wrong", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " I should order you to come with me. You'd never refuse an order", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I'm part of it as. long as you are", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "That's...two I owe ya", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Two. Remember? 'Eve", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Any time. How do we get back UP", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "We have a real problem here, my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Me too, man. This ain't nothin' I signed on for", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Wait here? No. We're gettin' out", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "If they're dead, they're dead. If they're alive, they'll still be alive in twenty minutes. When we get back", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "We don't. But we'll do our damndest to try. This is it, guys. The home stretch. Let's go", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " We're close. I think I'll be able to get the package. It's been... very interesting", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "  There's nothing I can't handle", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " How old are you", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "None of us is old enough for that", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Head shots. Ain't doin' nothin'", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What idea", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No, ma'am. Men like me... are just errand boys. Sent in to do the we", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes. I think it could be turned into five or ten million dollars. How do we get into", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No. It.. it can't be shut down", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You won't come out in the same place. But you'll find a freight loader that can be accessed with..", "docId": "Resident-Evil.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No. Pot blue or green. Red", "qsentId": 30}]